One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
עושר, תהילה, כוח...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
גולד רוג'ר, מלך הפיראטים, השיג את כל מה שהיה לעולם להציע.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
מה שאמר ברגעיו האחרונים דחף אינספור נשמות להפליג באוקינוס.
You want my treasure?
רוצים את האוצר שלי?
Go ahead.
קדימה.
Find it!
מצאו אותו!
Everything is right where I left it!
הכל נמצא היכן שהשארתי אותו!
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
עינהם של האנשים נישאו אל הקו הגדול במרדף אחר החלומות שלהם.
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
העולם אכן נכנס לעידן הפיראטים הגדול!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
One Piece! ONE PIECE
One Piece! ONE PIECE
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
When the world's got you down,
When the world's got you down,
Kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
Kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
WE ARE!
WE ARE!
Captain Kuro of a Thousand Plans
קפטן קורו בעל אלף התוכניות
What was that?!
מה זה היה?!
What did he do?!
מה הוא עשה?!
It looked like his arm stretched!
נראה כאילו הזרוע שלו נמתחה!
Get real!
תפסיק לחלום!
He knocked Captain Kuro flat on his ass!
הוא החטיף לקפטן קורו כל כך חזק שהוא עף!
I leave the rest to you...
אשאיר לך את השאר...
so leave the treasure to me!
אז תשאיר לי את השלל!
– The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
– הפיראטים של אוסופ הגיעו!
Guys!
חבר'ה!
Stay back!
אל תתקרבו!
Say your prayers, butt-ler!
תתפלל, משרת-תחת!
You had it coming!
מגיע לך!
A dumb pirate like you disturbing the peace...!
פיראטים מטומטמים שעושים לנו צרות...!
S-Stop!
ע-עצרו!
What the hell do you brats think you're doing?!
מה לעזאזל אתם חושבים שאתם עושים, פרחחים?!
What're those kids doing?!
מה הצוציקים האלו עושים?!
Stop that, you guys... Stop!
תפסיקו עם זה, חבר'ה... מספיק!
Alright! We'll let you off with just that!
בסדר! חטפת מספיק!
C-Captain Kuro has gotta be fuming now!
ק-קפטן קורו רותח בוודאות!
Captain, you came after all!
קפטן, באת למרות הכל!
You were fighting back for real!
באמת נלחמת בהם!
Why didn't you tell us?!
למה לא אמרת לנו?!
We fell by the waste side!
לא ספרת לנו!
No, it's "wayside," not "waste side"!
לא, זה לא ספרת "אותנו"!
Who cares which side?!
למה שאספור אתכם?!
Guys, just get the hell out of here!
חבר'ה, פשוט תברחו מכאן!
Run!
רוצו!
No way!
אין מצב!
We're gonna fight, too!
גם אנחנו נילחם!
Running will bring shame to the Usopp Pi–
זו תהיה בושה אם הפיראטים של אוסופ יברח-
Just hurry up and run, you idiots!
תזיזו את התחת שלכם ותברחו כבר, אידיוטים!
– Captain!
– קפטן!
That hurt a bit...
זה דיי כאב...
What a strange fighting technique...
איזה סגנון לחימה מוזר...
Can I assume...
אני מניח...
that you have devil fruit powers?!
שיש לך כוח של פרי שטן?!
Yep! I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
כן! אכלתי את פרי הגומי-גומי!
I'm a rubber man!
אני איש גומי!
What?! A devil fruit?!
מה?! פרי שטן?!
Then he's bad news!
אז הוא מסוכן!
Devil fruits really exist?!
פירות שטן באמת קיימים?!
I knew he seemed off!
ידעתי שמשהו מוזר!
A rubber man, huh?
איש גומי, הא?
So I didn't hallucinate his arm stretching...
אז לא דמיינתי שהזרועות שלו נמתחו...
Jango!
ג'אנגו!
Y-Yeah?
כ-כן?
The brat is mine.
הפרחח הזה שלי.
You take care of Miss Kaya.
טפל בגברת קאיה.
As planned, get her to write her will...
כמו שתכננתי, גרום לה לחתום על הצוואה...
then eliminate her!
ואז חסל אותה!
As for the three little mice...
בנוגע לשלושת העכברים...
They're a nuisance!
אין בהם צורך!
Consider it done.
אדאג לזה.
Stop.
עצור.
I'm afraid I can't let you pass.
אני חושש שאני לא יכול לתת לך לעבור.
Buchi!
בוצ'י!
Cat Astrophe!
מיצי-מיצי בום!
Not again!
לא שוב!
He's completely different from before...
הוא שונה לגמרי מלפני כן!
Crap!
שיט!
Dammit...
לעזאזל...
I can't even lift a finger...
אני לא מסוגל להרים אפילו אצבע!
Dammit... Dammit...
לעזאזל... לעזאזל...
Damn...
אוף...
Usopp Pirates!
הפיראטים של אוסופ!
– Y-Yes, sir?!
– כ-כן, המפקד?!
Listen to your captain!
זו פקודה מהקפטן!
We're not gonna run!
אנחנו לא נברח!
After what they did to you...
אחרי מה שהם עשו לך...
...we'll avenge you!
...אנחנו ננקום בשמך!
Protect Kaya!
תגנו על קאיה!
Listen closely!
תקשיבו טוב!
I'm giving you...
אני נותן לכם...
I'm giving you the most important part of the mission!
אני נותן לכם את החלק הכי חשוב במשימה!
Take Kaya and get away from here!
קחו את קאיה והסתלקו מכאן!
Don't tell me you can't!
אל תתווכחו איתי!
Remember why we formed our pirate crew!
זכרו למה הקמנו את צוות הפיראטים שלנו!
To become the kind of men who can protect what's important to us!
כדי להפוך לגברים שמסוגלים להגן על מי שחשובים לנו!
Usopp...
אוסופ...
That's... a direct order from your captain...
זו פקודה ישירה מהקפטן!
– Aye, aye, Captain!
– כן, כן, קפטן!
Hurry, Miss Kaya!
מהר, גברת קאיה!
This way! This way!
מהכיוון הזה!
This way!
מכאן!
He definitely has a way with words...
הוא בהחלט יודע לדבר...
His little speech got them to run...!
הנאום שלו גרם להם לברוח...!
These woods are like our backyard!
החורשה הזו היא כמו החצר שלנו!
Okay...
בסדר...
Jango!
ג'אנגו!
Ah, I was mesmerized!
אה, הייתי מהופנט!
They're fools if they think they can get awa–
הם טיפשים אם הם חושבים שיצליחו לברו-
How's that?
מה דעתך?
You damn bastard!
ממזר מקולל!
After them, you moron!
אחריהם, אידיוט!
Fine!
בסדר!
An exercise in futility...
כזה מאמץ לחינם...
If I know anything, it's how weak Kaya is.
אם יש משהו שאני יודע, זה כמה קאיה חלשה.
She'll never escape Jango.
היא לעולם לא תחמוק מג'אנגו.
If you want to help her, go right ahead.
אם אתה רוצה לעזור לה, מוזמן לנסות.
Not that you can get up this hill alive anyway.
לא שתצליח לעזוב את הגבעה הזו בחיים.
Buchi!
בוצ'י!
You already lost to me once!
הפסדת לי כבר פעם אחת!
Quit wasting my time!
אתה מבזבז לי את הזמן!
Get lost!
עוף מפה!
Is that hypnotist still following us?!
המהפנט ההוא עדיין מאחורינו?!
Nope, I don't see him!
לא, אני לא רואה אותו!
Let's lose him for good!
בואו נאבד אותו לגמרי!
As if he can catch us in this forest!
כאילו שהוא מסוגל לתפוס אותנו ביער!
Don't worry, Miss Kaya!
אל תדאגי, גברת קאיה!
We'll keep you safe!
נשמור עליך בטוחה!
Yeah! We swear on the name of the Usopp Pirates!
כן! אנחנו נשבעים בשם הפיראטים של אוסופ!
Thank you...
תודה לכם...
No sign of them...
אין סימן מהם...
Where'd you go, you twerps?!
לאן ברחתם, פרעושים?!
You can't run forever!
אתם לא יכולים לרוץ לנצח!
I'll level this entire forest if that's what it takes!
אקצור את כל היער הזה אם זה מה שצריך!
Man...
בחיי...
He's pretty pissed...
הוא דיי עצבני...
He's not just a hypnotist?!
הוא לא סתם מהפנט?!
Where did you run off to?
לאן ברחתם?
Over there!
שם!
Wh-What's that sound?!
מ-מה הצליל הזה?!
Who knows?
מי יודע?
Jango is probably tearing the place up.
נראה שג'אנגו מפרק את המקום.
Why not go and see for yourself?
למה שלא תלך לבדוק?
Though it may already be too late...
למרות שזה כנראה מאוחר מידי...
Damn you...!
לעזאזל אתך...!
Don't you even have a shred of pity?!
אין לך אפילו קמצוץ של רחמים?!
You lived with her for three years!
חיית איתה במשך שלוש שנים!
None!
לא!
Mind you, Kaya is nothing more than a pawn in my plan.
לידיעתך, קאיה היא לא יותר מבורג קטן בתוכנית שלי.
I'll thank her once she's dead.
אגיד לה תודה ברגע שהיא תמות.
Damn you...!
לעזאזל אתך...!
You can't save someone that evil...
אי אפשר לשכנע מישהו כזה רקוב...
I don't plan to save him, though.
מזל שאני לא מתכוון לשכנע אותו.
Usopp!
אוסופ!
Go help them!
לך לעזור להם!
We'll take over here!
אני אנקה כאן!
Leave it to us!
תשאיר את זה לנו!
Oh? You can still move? How impressive.
הו? מסוגל עדיין לזוז? מרשים מאוד...
Shut up...!
שתוק...!
I refuse...
אני מסרב...
to let you get away with this!
לתת לך להתחמק מעונש!
You went and betrayed the villagers'— betrayed Kaya's feelings!
בגדת באמון התושבים - בגדת ברגשות של קאיה!
I refuse to let you get away with any more of your plans!
אני מסרב לתת לך לחמוק מעונש או לזמום עוד מזימות!
Usopp!
אוסופ!
D-Dammit...
ל-לעזאזל...
I... can't move...
אני... לא יכול לזוז...
You really are quite amusing!
אתה באמת משעשע!
Just stay there on the ground.
פשוט תישאר שם על האדמה.
Though, even if you did catch up with Jango,
למרות שאפילו אם תצליח להשיג את ג'אנגו,
you'd be no match for him anyway.
לא יהיה לך סיכוי מולו.
This is likely the safest option for you!
כנראה יותר בטוח לך כאן!
Even if I am no match...
אפילו אם אין לי סיכוי...
Even if I am no match for him...
אפילו אם אין לי סיכוי מולו...
I will protect them!
אני אגן עליהם!
I'm the captain of the Usopp Pirates,
אני הקפטן של הפיראטים של אוסופ!
and I'm going to be a brave warrior of the sea!
ואני אהיה לוחם ים אמיץ!
I won't let you lay a finger on the village!
אני לא אתן לך לגעת בשערה מהראשים של התושבים!
What's with him?
מה יש לו?
He's yellin' somethin'!
הוא צועק משהו!
Check it out, he's cryin'!
תראו אותו, הוא בוכה!
What's so funny?!
מה מצחיק?!
Luffy!
לופי!
Me and Usopp are gonna chase that hypno-freak! That a problem?!
אני ואוסופ נטפל במהפנט הפריק! יש לך בעיה עם זה?!
Nope! Hurry!
לא! קדימה!
I-I'm sorry about this...
ס-סליחה על זה...
I'd actually be a lot faster by myself, but they're inside some woods.
אני אהיה מהיר יותר לבד, אבל הם ביער.
I'm gonna need your directions to catch up to him.
אני אצטרך הכוונה כדי להשיג אותם.
Hold it, you two.
עצרו, שניכם.
Who gave you permission to climb this hill?
מי נתן לכם רשות לטפס על הגבעה הזו?
I did!
אני!
Go! Zoro! Usopp!
קדימה! זורו! אוסופ!
And another!
ועוד אחד!
Gum-Gum Spear!
גומי-גומי רומח!
Dammit! He disappeared again!
לעזאזל, הוא נעלם שוב!
Oh, well! At least they made it up the hill!
נו טוב, לפחות הם עברו את המדרון!
Before we fight, I just have one question.
לפני שנלחם, יש לי שאלה אליך.
Why is an outsider like you sticking his nose into the village's business?!
למה זר כמוך דוחף את האף שלו לעניינים של הכפר?
Because there's someone in this village I don't want dying on me.
כי יש מישהו בכפר הזה שאני לא רוצה שימות.
How simple.
כמה פשוט.
Are you sure you want that to be the reason you die?
אתה בטוח שאתה רוצה למות בשביל סיבה כזו?
Yep!
יאפ!
I'm not gonna die, though!
אבל אני לא הולך למות!
I'll make sure you do!
אני אוודא שכן!
Gum-Gum Whip!
גומי-גומי שוט!
And Pistol!
ואקדח!
What a bore!
כמה משעמם!
Why, you...!
חתיכת...!
Hey! East! East! I said east!
היי! מזרח! מזרח! אמרתי מזרח!
That's not helpful! Tell me left or right!
זה לא עוזר! תגיד לי ימין או שמאל!
Then, turn right!
אז תפנה ימינה!
That's the opposite way!
זה הכיוון ההפוך!
Miss Kaya!
גברת קאיה!
I'm sorry...
אני מצטערת...
You run on ahead...
תמשיכו בלעדיי...
What are you saying?!
מה את מקשקשת?!
Our mission is to protect you!
המשימה שלנו היא להגן עליך!
Oh no! She's got a really bad fever!
הו לא! יש לה חום ממש גבוה!
What?! Hang in there, Miss Kaya!
מה?! תחזיקי מעמד, גברת קאיה!
A doctor...! Get a doctor!
רופא...! צריך למצוא רופא!
You dummy! Like we have time for that!
טמבל! כאילו שיש לנו זמן לזה!
Someone's trying to kill her!
מישהו מנסה להרוג אותה!
But it's dangerous for her to keep running!
אבל זה ממש מסוכן אם היא תמשיך לרוץ!
But...
אבל...
Where are you, you twerps?!
איפה אתם, פרעושים?!
Thank you...
תודה לכם...
I'm happy that you helped me...
אני שמחה שעזרתם לי...
Just the thought is enough for me...
רק הכוונה מספיקה עבורי...
Run away, all three of you.
רוצו, שלושתכם.
Where did you run off to?
לאן ברחתם?
If we leave Miss Kaya and run, we'll probably survive, right?
אם נעזוב את גברת קאיה ונברח, כנראה נשרוד, נכון?
Yeah, probably.
כן, כנראה.
Our captain always says to run with your tail between your legs if you're gonna lose...
הקפטן תמיד אומר לברוח עם הזנב בין הרגליים אם עומדים להפסיד...
Our captain is a liar after all!
אבל הקפטן שלנו גם שקרן!
Even he went and fought!
אפילו הוא נשאר ונלחם!
He tried so hard to protect us!
הוא התאמץ ממש להגן עלינו!
We won't let Miss Kaya die!
לא ניתן לגברת קאיה למות!
Alright then! Prepare yourselves, Usopp Pirates!
החלטנו! היכונו, הפיראטים של אוסופ!
Yeah!
כן!
Let's fight him!
בואו נילחם בו!
No!
לא!
You're still just children!
אתם רק ילדים!
You mustn't die for my sake!
אסור לכם למות בשבילי!
We're not gonna die.
אנחנו לא נמות.
We're gonna fight to live!
נילחם כדי לחיות!
Damn...
לעזאזל...
He cut my mouth...
הוא חתך את הפה שלי...
That straw hat guy's insanely strong, and yet...
הבחור עם כובע הקש חזק בטירוף, ועדיין...
Th-That's Captain Kuro for ya!
זו הרמה של קפטן קורו!
Get 'im!
תראה לו!
Hurray for Captain Kuro!
הידד לקפטן קורו!
Captain Kuro!
קפטן קורו!
You're awesome, Captain Kuro!
אתה מדהים, קפטן קורו!
Don't call me by that name!
אל תקראו לי בשם הזה!
Do you still not understand?!
לא הבנתם עדיין?!
The culmination of this plan entirely rids me of the name "Captain Kuro"!
כל המטרה של התוכנית הזו היא להפטר מהשם "קפטן קורו"!
I'm tired...
התעייפתי...
Each and every day, devising plans for men who only care about mayhem...
יום אחרי יום, לתכנן תוכניות בשביל אנשים שאיכפת להם רק מהרס!
with government dogs and bounty hunters nipping at my heels...
כלבים של הממשלה וציידי ראשים מזדנבים אחריי כל הזמן...
I was absolutely sick of it all!
נמאס לי מכל זה כבר!
The Marines, huh...?
הצי, הא...?
Kuro of a Thousand Plans (3 Years Ago)
תוינכותה ףלא לעב ורוק (םינש 3 ינפל)
This is the third time this week...
זו הפעם השלישית השבוע...
That's how it goes.
אין מה לעשות.
We're doing stuff that makes people chase us.
אנחנו עושים דברים שגורמים לאנשים לרדוף אותנו.
Plus, you've made quite a name for yourself...
מה גם שצברת שם לעצמך...
Yes...
כן...
That name is what draws them to us.
השם הזה הוא מה שמושך אותם אלינו.
That's why I'm giving up being Captain Kuro.
זה למה אני מוותר על להיות קפטן קורו.
That's a good one.
בדיחה טובה.
But it's no use.
אבל אין טעם.
The Marines won't stand down until you're dead.
הצי לא יוותרו עד שתמות.
I am going to die.
לכן אני אמות.
It would seem a pirate's life is not for me...
נראה שחיי פיראט לא מתאימים לי.
But... you're the captain!
אבל... אתה הקפטן!
You can be captain!
אתה יכול להיות קפטן!
I'm sick of this tumultuous lifestyle.
יש לי בחילה מהחיים המציקים האלו.
I'm... going to kill myself for all to see!
אני... הולך להרוג את עצמי כך שכולם יראו!
Captain Kuro!
קפטן קורו!
Captain...
קפטן...
Captain!
קפטן!
How many vessels?
כמה ספינות?
J-Just one!
ר-רק אחת!
What should we do, Captain?
מה נעשה, קפטן?
Should we blast 'em back?
שנפציץ אותם בחזרה?
Lower a small boat.
תורידו סירה קטנה.
Huh?!
הא?!
Lower it!
סירה קטנה!
First Mate Jango! Captain Kuro...!
חובל ראשון ג'אנגו! קפטן קורו...!
Yeah, I know.
כן, אני יודע.
"You know"?!
"אתה יודע"?!
It's too risky to go there by himself!
זה מסוכן מידי לשוט לשם לבד!
Don't tell me he's turning himself in?!
אל תגידו לי שהוא מסגיר את עצמו?!
Huh?! The cannon fire stopped...
הא?! ירי התותחים פסק...
Dock with their ship.
עלו לספינה שלהם.
B-But...
א-אבל...
Just do as I say, dammit!
עשו מה שאני אומר, לעזאזל!
Y-Yes, sir!
כ-כן, בוס!
Hey, get ready to fight!
היי, היכון לקרב!
I see...
הבנתי...
Approach the ship! So that's why...
שוטו לספינה! אז זה למה...
Th-The Marines...
ה-הצי...
He wiped them all out!
הוא חיסל את כולם!
Now, then...
ועכשיו...
Let's get this plan underway...!
נתחיל בתוכנית...!
Hey, now. Pull yourself together.
היי, תתאפס על עצמך.
I was kind enough to leave you alive, you know...
הייתי אדיב כל כך להשאיר אותך בחיים אחרי הכל...
Sh-Shut up...
ש-שתוק...
I-I'm not gonna beg for my life...
א-אני לא מתכוון להתחנן על חיי...
F-Finish me off, damn you...
סיים עם זה כבר, לעזאזל אתך...
Looking good there.
לא רע בכלל.
If you can howl that much with a shattered jaw, then that's perfect!
אם אתה מסוגל לילל כל כך עם לסת שבורה, זה מושלם!
I'm giving you, a nameless, low-ranking soldier, a treat.
אני נותן לחייל זוטר כמוך פרס.
Be grateful and accept it...
קבל אותו בהכרת תודה...
The head of Kuro of a Thousand Plans!
ראשו של קורו בעל אלף התוכניות!
Your name is Captain Kuro.
שמך הוא קפטן קורו.
This atrocity was your doing.
הזוועה הזו היא מעשה ידיך.
One...
אחת...
two...
שתיים...
Jango!
ג'אנגו!
My name is Captain Kuro.
שמי הוא קפטן קורו.
This atrocity was my doing.
הזוועה הזו היא מעשה ידיי.
And you're the man who caught Captain Kuro.
ואתה מי שלכד את קפטן קורו.
Return to base and execute this man.
חזור לבסיס והוצא אותו להורג.
One...
אחת...
two...
שתיים...
Jango!
ג'אנגו!
I'm the man who caught Captain Kuro!
אני הגבר שלכד את קפטן קורו!
You're doing it again, First Mate!
אתה שוב עושה את זה, חובל ראשון!
Perfect...
מושלם...
With my replacement gone, Captain Kuro will disappear from the world.
עכשיו כשהכפיל שלי יחוסל, קפטן קורו יעלם מעל פני האדמה.
And today, when my plan succeeds, my goal will be fully realized...!
והיום, כשהתוכנית שלי תצליח, המטרה שלי תתממש במלואה...!
I'll have both money and peace of mind.
יהיו לי גם ממון וגם שלווה!
Do you understand, boy?
אתה מבין, ילד?
I cannot allow this plan of three years to fail!
אני לא יכול לתת לתוכנית הזו להכשל אחרי שלוש שנים!
My plan will not be disrupted!
התוכנית שלי לא תשתבש!
Seems you can do more than just stretch!
נראה שאתה מסוגל לעשות יותר מסתם להמתח!
That's right!
נכון מאוד!
I've toughened myself up to be a pirate!
התאמנתי קשה כדי להיות פיראט!
You're "tired"?!
"התעייפת"?!
If you can't handle a reputation on the seas, you shouldn't be a pirate!
אם תשומת הלב בים מפריעה לך, אתה לא צריך להיות פיראט!
Your ambition...
השאיפות שלך...
doesn't even compare to my own!
לא משתוות בכלל לשאיפות שלי!